Guide to the Kenneth Scott Latourette Papers
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Writings - Addendum, Series VI
  - Published Writings
    - "Far Eastern Studies at Yale" in Amerasia, 1938 (Box 168, Folder 83)
    - "The Madras Conference of the International Missionary Council" in The Crozer Quarterly, 1939 (Box 168, Folder 83)
    - "In Determining its Character" in The Evanston Series, 1941 (Box 168, Folder 83)
    - "New Perspectives in Church History" in The Journal of Religion, 1941 (Box 168, Folder 83)
    - "The Christian Church in the Last Seventy Years" in American Historical Association, Annual Report, 1942 (Box 168, Folder 83)
    - "Samuel Wells Williams" in Far Eastern Studies, 1943 (Box 168, Folder 84)
    - "Problems Confronting Christian Missionaries in the Far East" in Pacific Affairs, 1948 (Box 168, Folder 84)
    - "Troubled Times for Religion" in The Yale Daily New Review of the Year, 1951 (Box 168, Folder 84)
    - "Christian Adventure at Yale" in Celebration of the Seventy-Fifth Anniversary of the Founding of the Yale Young Men's Christian Association, 1956 (Box 168, Folder 84)
    - "The Christian World Mission in Our Day", in The Outlook, 1958 (Box 168, Folder 84)
    - "Developments in the 'Younger Churches' since Edinburgh, 1910", 1960 (Box 168, Folder 84)
    - "The Influence of the Reformation on World History" in Christianity Today, 1967 (Box 168, Folder 85)
    - "Problems and Trends of the Modern Theological World" (in Korean) in Christian Thought, 1967 (Box 168, Folder 85)
    - "Robert Speer - Great Missionary Statesman" in Covenant Companion, 1967 (Box 168, Folder 85)
    - "Perspective on the World Mission" (for American Baptist Foreign Mission Society), n.d. (Box 168, Folder 86)
    - "What Can I Believe about Christian Missions?" (for Student Volunteer Movement), n.d. (Box 168, Folder 86)
    - "The Missionary Thinking of Francis Xavier" in The Student World, n.d. (Box 168, Folder 86)
    - Correspondence of the Reverend Ezra Fisher by KSL et al (Box 168, Folder 87)
    - "We Must Continue and Strengthen Foreign Missions" (for Foreign Missions Conference of North America) (Box 168, Folder 86)